

### EDUCATION

UC San Diego Extension UX Design Certificate Program 2018 - 2019

> **UC Santa Barbara** B.S. Biological Sciences 2012 - 2014

### SKILLS

Sketch Illustrator Photoshop InDesign InVision HTML/CSS

User Research

Wireframes

Iterative Design

Prototyping

**Petting Cats** 

#### PROFILE

I'm a designer in the truest sense of the world. With over six years of graphic/visual design experience and two years of UX design, I've been responsible for strengthening visual identities and building products with a user-first mentality.

### EXPERIENCE

# Visual Designer | Engagio

Jan. 2018 - Present

- San Mateo, CA
- Own website design to bring user-friendliness and simplicity
- Create wireframes, userflows, and personas to communicate ideas
- Design print material for marketing collateral and graphics for ads

## Visual Designer | SF Hep B Free San Francisco, CA

Dec. 2017 - Present

- Provide print and digital designs for ads, posters, infographics, brochures and other things for Asian health nonprofit
- Help organization conceptualize ideas to communicate to health professionals about hepatitis B

# UX/Product Designer | Controlco

Sep. 2016 - Oct. 2017

Pleasant Hill, CA

- Created IoT applications using HTML/CSS, Niagara 4 and DGLux5
- Provided wireframes and user storyboards to communicate design
- Brought new design initiatives and UX best practices to products

### Freelance Designer

2012 - Present

• Design everything from digital illustrations, logos, banners, t-shirts, icons, and UI assets for web and mobile